A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Projects, International Relations, RG 1.3, Series 155 FA388A
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International Relations, 1971-1989; 155
  - Conflict in International Relations - Fellowships, 155E
    - Bruce Parrott: Supplementary Material (II), 1977 May-June (Box 134, Folder 1366)
    - Bruce Parrott: Supplementary Material (III): "Technological Progress and Soviet Politics", 1977 Spring (Box 134, Folder 1367)
    - Bruce Parrott: Supplementary Material (IV): "Politics and Technology in the Soviet Union", pp. i-vii, Chapter 1-2, no date (Box 134, Folder 1368)
    - Bruce Parrott: Supplementary Material (V): "Politics and Technology in the Soviet Union", Chapter 3, no date (Box 134, Folder 1369)
    - Bruce Parrott: Supplementary Material (VI): "Politics and Technology in the Soviet Union", Chapter 4, no date (Box 134, Folder 1370)
    - Bruce Parrott: Supplementary Material (VII): "Politics and Technology in the Soviet Union", Chapter 5, no date (Box 134, Folder 1371)
    - Bruce Parrott: Supplementary Material (VIII): "Politics and Technology in the Soviet Union", Chapters 6-7, no date (Box 134, Folder 1372)
    - Vratislav Pěchota: Front of File and Evaluation, 1977-1980, 1983-1984 (Box 134, Folder 1373)
    - Vratislav Pěchota, 1977-1979 (Box 134, Folder 1374)
    - Vratislav Pěchota, 1980 (Box 135, Folder 1375)
    - Barry R. Posen, 1981-1987, 1990 (Box 135, Folder 1376)
    - Rasul B. Rais, 1983-1985, 1990, 1992 (Box 135, Folder 1377)
    - Rasul B. Rais, 1980 (Box 135, Folder 1377A)
    - J. Mohan Rao, 1982-1987, 1990 (Box 135, Folder 1378)
    - J. Mohan Rao, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 1378A)
    - Anibal Romero, 1982-1986 (Box 135, Folder 1379)
    - Anibal Romero: Supplementary Material (I): "Venezuela: Democracia, Estrategia Nacional y Politica Exterior", pp. i-iii, 1-72, 1984 (Box 135, Folder 1380)
    - Anibal Romero: Supplementary Material (II): "Venezuela: Democracia, Estrategia Nacional y Politica Exterior", pp. 73-159, 1984 (Box 135, Folder 1381)
    - Anibal Romero: Supplementary Material (III): "Venezuela: Democracia, Estrategia Nacional y Politica Exterior", pp. 160-237, 1984 (Box 135, Folder 1382)
    - Anibal Romero: Supplementary Material (IV): "Venezuela: Democracia, Estrategia Nacional y Politico Exterior", pp. 238-314, 1984 (Box 135, Folder 1383)
    - Anibal Romero: Supplementary Material (V): "Venezuela: Democracia, Estrategia Nacional y Politico Exterior", pp. 315-398, 1984 (Box 135, Folder 1384)
    - Reinhardt Rummel: Front of File, 1980-1981, 1983, 1984 (Box 136, Folder 1385)
    - Reinhardt Rummel, 1978-1981 (Box 136, Folder 1386)
    - Reinhardt Rummel, 1982-1983 (Box 136, Folder 1387)
    - Nadav Safran: Front of File, 1979, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 1388)
    - Nadav Safran, 1974, 1977-1978 (Box 136, Folder 1389)
    - Nadav Safran, 1979-1980, 1982-1983 (Box 136, Folder 1390)
    - Amin Saikal: Front of File, 1982-1984, 1986-1987, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 1391)
    - Amin Saikal, 1981-1984 February (Box 136, Folder 1392)
    - Amin Saikal, 1984 May-1988 September (Box 136, Folder 1393)
    - Amin Saikal: Supplementary Material (I): "Khomeini's Iran", 1983 October (Box 136, Folder 1394)
    - Amin Saikal: Supplementary Material (II): "The Pakistan Disturbances and the Afghanistan Problem", no date (Box 136, Folder 1395)
    - Amin Saikal: Supplementary Material (III): "The Conceptual Origins and Interpretations of 'Islamic Socialism'", no date (Box 136, Folder 1396)
    - Amin Saikal: Supplementary Material (IV): "The Method of Soviet Intervention: The Cases of Poland and Afghanistan", no date (Box 136, Folder 1397)
    - Amin Saikal: Supplementary Material (V): "The Foreign Policy of Iran, 1921-1979", no date (Box 136, Folder 1398)
    - Ghassan Salamé, 1982-1986, 1989, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 1399)
    - Steven E. Sanderson: Front of File, 1981-1982, 1984 (Box 136, Folder 1400)
    - Steven E. Sanderson, 1980-1982 (Box 136, Folder 1401)
    - Steven E. Sanderson, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 1402)
    - Steven E. Sanderson: Supplementary Material (I): "Florida Tomatoes, U. S.-Mexican Relations, and the International Division of Labor", 1980 (Box 137, Folder 1403)
    - Steven E. Sanderson: Supplementary Material (II): "Food Crops, Fodder, and Fresh Meat: The Politics of the Beef Cattle Industry and its Importance for U. S.-Mexican Relations in the 1980s" (Box 137, Folder 1404)
    - Steven E. Sanderson: Supplementary Material (III): "Agrarian Populism and the Mexican State", pp. i-xvii, 1-127, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 1405)
    - Steven E. Sanderson: Supplementary Material (IV): "Agrarian Populism and the Mexican State", pp. 128-243, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 1406)
    - Mitchell A. Seligson, 1982-1987, 1989, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 1407)
    - Sallama Shaker: Front of File and Evaluation, 1983-1984, 1986, 1988, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 1408)
    - Sallama Shaker, 1983 January-1984 June (Box 137, Folder 1409)
    - Sallama Shaker, 1984 July-1986 November (Box 137, Folder 1410)
    - Sallama Shaker: Supplementary Material (I): "Egypt and Turkey: Great Power Rivalry and Regional Stability in the Middle East", Chapter I, 1985 March (Box 137, Folder 1411)
    - Sallama Shaker: Supplementary Material (II): "Egypt and Turkey: Great Power Rivalry and Regional Stability in the Middle East", Chapter II, 1985 March (Box 137, Folder 1412)
    - Sallama Shaker: Supplementary Material (III): "Egypt and Turkey: Great Power Rivalry and Regional Stability in the Middle East", Chapter III, 1985 March (Box 137, Folder 1413)
    - Sallama Shaker: Supplementary Material (IV): "Egypt and Turkey: Great Power Rivalry and Regional Stability in the Middle East", Chapter IV, 1985 March (Box 137, Folder 1414)
    - Sallama Shaker: Supplementary Material (V): "Egypt and Turkey: Great Power Rivalry and Regional Stability in the Middle East", Appendices I-XIV, 1985 March (Box 137, Folder 1415)
    - Susan L. Shirk, 1983 January-1986 June, 1989 November, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 1416)
    - Paul B. Stares, 1981 October-1985 September, 1986 (Box 138, Folder 1417)
    - David W. Tarr, 1976-1979, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 1418)
    - Kosta Tsipis: Front of File and Evaluation, 1977, 1979, 1985-1986 (Box 138, Folder 1419)
    - Kosta Tsipis, 1974 December-1977 February (Box 138, Folder 1420)
    - Kosta Tsipis, 1977 April-1980 December (Box 138, Folder 1421)
    - Kosta Tsipis: Supplementary Material (I), 1975, 1977, 1978 (Box 138, Folder 1422)
    - Kosta Tsipis: Supplementary Material (II): "Arsenal: Understanding Weapons in the Nuclear Age", 1983 (Box 138, Folder 1423)
    - Taketsugu Tsurutani, 1979-1984 (Box 138, Folder 1424)
    - Taketsugu Tsurutani: Supplementary Material (I): "The Causes of Paralysis"; "Uncertain Future of Sino-Japanese Relations"; "Defense of Japan and U. S.-Japanese Security Cooperation in the Western Pacific", 1974, no date (Box 138, Folder 1425)
    - Taketsugu Tsurutani: Supplementary Material (II): "Political Change in Japan", 1977 (Box 138, Folder 1426)
    - Taketsugu Tsurutani: Supplementary Material (III): "Security Debate in Japan", 1978 (Box 139, Folder 1427)
    - Taketsugu Tsurutani: Supplementary Material (IV): "Japan's Security Responsibility and Defense Capability", 1981 (Box 139, Folder 1428)
    - Taketsugu Tsurutani: Supplementary Material (V): "East Asian Security and Japanese Policy in the 1980s", Chapters One and Two (Box 139, Folder 1429)
    - Taketsugu Tsurutani: Supplementary Material (VI): "East Asian Security and Japanese Policy in the 1980s", Chapter Three (Box 139, Folder 1430)
    - Taketsugu Tsurutani: Supplementary Material (VII): "East Asian Security and Japanese Policy in the 1980s", Chapter Four (Box 139, Folder 1431)
    - Taketsugu Tsurutani: Supplementary Material (VIII): "East Asian Security and Japanese Policy in the 1980s", Chapter Five (Box 139, Folder 1432)
    - Taketsugu Tsurutani: Supplementary Material (IX): "East Asian Security and Japanese Policy in the 1980s", Chapter Six (Box 139, Folder 1433)
    - Bernard Udis: Front of File and Evaluation, 1976, 1981, 1983 (Box 139, Folder 1434)
    - Bernard Udis, 1974 October-1976 July (Box 139, Folder 1435)
    - Bernard Udis, 1976 August-November (Box 139, Folder 1436)
    - Bernard Udis, 1977 January-1979 June (Box 139, Folder 1437)
    - Bernard Udis, 1979 July-1981 July (Box 139, Folder 1438)
    - Bernard Udis: Supplementary Material, 1973, no date (Box 139, Folder 1439)
    - United Nations Institute for Training and Research: Theodor Meron: Front of File, 1974, 1983 (Box 139, Folder 1440)
    - United Nations Institute for Training and Research: Theodor Meron, 1973-1974 (Box 139, Folder 1441)
    - United Nations Institute for Training and Research: Theodor Meron, 1975 January-1976 March (Box 140, Folder 1442)
    - United Nations Institute for Training and Research: Theodor Meron, 1976 November-1977 December, 1979 May-1980 February, 1982 March-April (Box 140, Folder 1443)
    - United Nations Institute for Training and Research: Theodor Meron: Supplementary Material (I), 1960, 1966, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 1444)
    - United Nations Institute for Training and Research: Theodor Meron: Supplementary Material (II): "The United Nations Secretariat: The Rules and the Game", 1976 (Box 140, Folder 1445)
    - United Nations Institute for Training and Research: Theodor Meron: Supplementary Material (III): "The United Nations Secretariat: The Rules and the Practice", pp. i-xvi, 1-80, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 1446)
    - United Nations Institute for Training and Research: Theodor Meron: Supplementary Material (IV): "The United Nations Secretariat: The Rules and the Practice", pp. 81-183, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 1447)
    - United Nations Institute for Training and Research: Theodor Meron: Supplementary Material (V): "The United Nations Secretariat: The Rules and the Practice", pp. 184-290, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 1448)
    - United Nations Institute for Training and Research: Theodor Meron: Supplementary Material (VI): "The United Nations Secretariat: The Rules and the Practice", pp. 291-359, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 1449)
    - Jiri Valenta, 1980-1985, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 1450)
    - Jiri Valenta: Supplementary Material (I): "From Prague to Kabul: The Soviet Style of Invasion", 1980 (Box 141, Folder 1451)
    - Jiri Valenta: Supplementary Material (II): "Soviet Options in Poland", 1981 (Box 141, Folder 1452)
    - Jiri Valenta: Supplementary Material (III): "Soviet Policy toward Hungary and Czechoslovakia: Invasions and Beyond", 1981 (Box 141, Folder 1453)
    - Naomi Joy Weinberger: Front of File, 1982-1984, 1986 (Box 141, Folder 1454)
    - Naomi Joy Weinberger, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 1455)
    - Naomi Joy Weinberger, 1982-1985 (Box 141, Folder 1456)
    - Allen S. Whiting: Front of File and Evaluation, 1978, 1982-1983 (Box 142, Folder 1457)
    - Allen S. Whiting, 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 1458)
    - Allen S. Whiting: Supplementary Material: "Siberian Development and East Asia", 1981 (Box 142, Folder 1459)
    - Gilbert R. Winham, 1977, 1979-1984 (Box 142, Folder 1460)
    - Gilbert R. Winham: Supplementary Material (I), 1976-1977, no date (Box 142, Folder 1461)
    - Gilbert R. Winham: Supplementary Material (II), 1978 (Box 142, Folder 1462)
    - Gilbert R. Winham: Supplementary Material (III): "Robert Strauss, the MTN, and the Control of Faction", 1979, 1980 (Box 142, Folder 1463)
    - Gilbert R. Winham: Supplementary Material (IV): "From Trade Policy to Investment Policy: The United States, Japan and Automobiles, 1980", 1980 September (Box 142, Folder 1464)
    - Gilbert R. Winham: Supplementary Material (V): "The United States wine gallon concession: how the biggest chip in the Tokyo Round was negotiated", 1981 Autumn (Box 142, Folder 1465)
    - Gilbert R. Winham: Supplementary Material (VI): "International Trade and the Tokyo Round", Chapter 2 - Background to the Negotiations, no date (Box 142, Folder 1466)
    - Fellowship Applications: Lee Lai To; John H. Maier; Gerald Segal, 1980 (Box 142, Folder 1467)